Nancy Sweezy collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 3: Southern Pottery Interviews; Raised in Clay, 1967-1995, Bulk: 1981-1994
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Printed material re: North Carolina potters from Dot Auman, undated (Box-folder 54/6-7)
    - The Meaders family, North Georgia potters by Rinzler and Sayers [inscribed to Nancy Sweezy from Ralph Rinzler], 1980 (Box-folder 89/4)
    - Folklife Festival: The 1982 World's Fair - Knoxville,Tennessee booklet, 1982 (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Contracts and material re: Southern pottery work for Smithsonian, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 54/8)
    - SITES (Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service) exhibit papers, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 54/9-12)
    - SITES (Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service) exhibit papers, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 55/1-4)
    - Smithsonian book ( Raised in Clay, 1984) papers, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 55/5-8)
    - Smithsonian book ( Raised in Clay, 1984) papers, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 55/9)
    - Book notes, 1983 (Box-folder 55/10)
    - Smithsonian communications re: book ( Raised in Clay, 1984), undated (Box-folder 55/11)
    - Clippings and book reviews, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 55/12-14)
    - Clippings and book reviews, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 56/1)
    - University of North Carolina ( Raised in Clay, 1994), 1994-1995 (Box-folder 56/2)
    - Preface-new edition ( Raised in Clay, 1994), undated (Box-folder 56/3)
    - Information from potters for new afterword ( Raised in Clay, 1994), undated (Box-folder 56/4)
    - Clippings and book reviews, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 56/5)
    - Southern Folk Pottery Collectors Society "Sweezy Day" Issue, 1994 (Box-folder 56/6)
    - Steve Abee contact sheets, undated, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/4)
    - Burlon Craig contact sheets, undated, 3 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/5)
    - Vernon Owens contact sheets, undated, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/6)
    - Joe Reinhardt and Charles Lisk contact sheets, 1998, 5 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/7)
    - Mark Hewitt contact sheet, undated, 1 photographic print (Box-folder 87/8)
    - Raised in Clay RTC contact sheets, undated, 40 photographic prints (Box-folder 86/9)
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Small and new kilns at Jugtown, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph06_001 to ph06_022 (Box 18)
    - Groundhog firing, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph06_023 to ph06_041 (Box 18)
    - T. Jackson, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph06_042 to ph06_056 (Box 18)
    - Shearwater / Biloxi, Mississippi, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph06_057 to ph06_081 (Box 18)
    - Danny Marley - Seagrove, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_001 to ph07_005 (Box 18-19)
    - Pisgah Forest, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_006 to ph07_013 (Box 18-19)
    - ML Owens - Seagrove, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph06_014 to ph07_028 (Box 18-19)
    - Auman - Seagrove Pottery, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph06_029 to ph07_036 (Box 18-19)
    - Burlon Craig - Vale, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_037 to ph07_045 (Box 18-19)
    - JB Cole - Seagrove, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_046 to ph07_053 (Box 18-19)
    - Celia Coles - Sanford, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_054 to ph07_065 (Box 18-19)
    - Jugtown - Jackson and RTC, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_066 to ph07_085 (Box 18-19)
    - Jugtown Pots - TG and RTC, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_086 to ph07_112 (Box 18-19)
    - Burning J, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_113 to ph07_130 (Box 18-19)
    - Westmoore/Seagrove, North Carolina, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph07_131 to ph07_145 (Box 18-19)
    - Jerry Brown - Alabama, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph08_001 to ph08_035 (Box 19-21)
    - Boggs - Alabama, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_036 to ph08_052 (Box 19-21)
    - Bybee - Kentucky, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_053 to ph08_099 (Box 19-21)
    - WJ Gordy - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_100 to ph08_145 (Box 19-21)
    - DX Gordy - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_146 to ph08_204 (Box 19-21)
    - Hewell - Georgia, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph08_205 to ph08_226 (Box 19-21)
    - Marshall Pottery - Texas, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph08_227 to ph08_259 (Box 19-21)
    - CL Meaders - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_260 to ph08_264 (Box 19-21)
    - Lanier Meaders - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_265 to ph08_298 (Box 19-21)
    - Edwin Meaders - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_299 to ph08_312 (Box 19-21)
    - Cleaver and Annie Meaders - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_313 to ph08_330 (Box 19-21)
    - Eric Miller - Alabama, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph08_331 to ph08_345 (Box 19-21)
    - Marie Rogers - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_346 to ph08_354 (Box 19-21)
    - Shearwater - Biloxi, Mississippi, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_355 to ph08_370 (Box 19-21)
    - Norman Smith, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_371 to ph08_404 (Box 19-21)
    - Gerald Stewart, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_405 to ph08_420 (Box 19-21)
    - Wilson Pottery - Georgia, 1982, AFC 2017/001: ph08_421 to ph08_434 (Box 19-21)
    - North Carolina pots, 1983, AFC 2017/001: ph09_004 to ph09_054 (Box 21)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - Meaders - Cleveland, Georgia / Terry King and Ben Owen III - Seagrove, North Carolina, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV20; 1 videotape
    - A.R. Cole; Sanford, North Carolina, 1973-07-15, AFC 2017/001: SR001; 1 audio cassette
    - Vernon Owens on turning, 1978-01-13, AFC 2017/001: SR002; 1 audio cassette
    - Mrs. Bertie Moore, 1979-03, AFC 2017/001: SR010; 1 audio cassette
    - John Burrison in Georgia potteries, 1980-03-20, AFC 2017/001: SR011; 1 audio cassette
    - Meeting at Children's Museum, 1980, AFC 2017/001: SR012; 1 audio cassette
    - Valerie Nicholson, 1981-02-03, AFC 2017/001: SR013; 1 audio cassette
    - Valerie Nicholson, 1981-02-12, AFC 2017/001: SR014; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Dot Auman / Side two: cont. Melvin Owens from 1981-03-25, 1982-03-25, AFC 2017/001: SR015; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview one with Charles Moore; Jugtown Pottery, 1982-06-28, AFC 2017/001: SR016; 1 audio cassette
    - Mabel Hussey no.1; Seagrove, North Carolina; Robbins, North Carolina, 1982-07-15, AFC 2017/001: SR017; 1 audio cassette
    - Side one: Nancy Owens (1983-06-24) / Side two: Boyd Owens (1982-07-16); Owens Pottery, 1982-07-16, AFC 2017/001: SR018; 1 audio cassette
    - Waymon Cole no. 3; Ashboro, North Carolina, 1982-07-19, AFC 2017/001: SR019; 1 audio cassette
    - Mabel Hussey no. 2; Robbins, North Carolina, 1982-07-21, AFC 2017/001: SR020; 1 audio cassette
    - Mabel and Rufus Hussey; Robbins, North Carolina, 1982-07-21, AFC 2017/001: SR021; 1 audio cassette
    - Scholars discussion no. 1: Pottery selection process with Susan Meyers, Terry Zug, John Burrison, Nancy Sweezy, Ralph Rinzler; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-01-15, AFC 2017/001: SR022; 1 audio cassette
    - Scholars discussion no. 2: Pottery selection process with Susan Meyers, Terry Zug, John Burrison, Nancy Sweezy, Ralph Rinzler; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-01-15, AFC 2017/001: SR023; 1 audio cassette
    - Scholars discussion no. 3: Pottery selection process with Susan Meyers, Terry Zug, John Burrison, Nancy Sweezy, Ralph Rinzler; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-01-15, AFC 2017/001: SR024; 1 audio cassette
    - Jerry Brown at his shop with Hank Willet, Joey Brackner, Mrs. Horace Brown), Sandra Brown), and Gerald Stewart's wife; Hamilton, Alabama, 1983-05-05, AFC 2017/001: SR025; 1 audio cassette
    - Jerry Brown no. 2 at his shop in with Hank Willet, Joey Brackner, Mrs. Horace Brown, Sandra Brown, and Gerald Stewart's wife; Hamilton, Alabama, 1983-05-05, AFC 2017/001: SR026; 1 audio cassette
    - Salt glaze workshop with Vernon Owens; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-05-13, AFC 2017/001: SR027; 1 audio cassette
    - Interview no. 3 with Melvin Owens; Side one: at Jugtown (1983-29-05) / Side two: at Owens Pottery (1983-06-24), 1983-05-29, AFC 2017/001: SR028; 1 audio cassette
    - Sidney Luck interview; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-06-24, AFC 2017/001: SR029; 1 audio cassette
    - Billy Ray Hussey at his shop; Robbins, North Carolina, 1983-06-25, AFC 2017/001: SR030; 1 audio cassette
    - Mark Chrisco at his shop; Seagrove, North Carolina, 1983-06-28, AFC 2017/001: SR031; 1 audio cassette
    - Arthur Staley; Jugtown Pottery, 1983-06-28, AFC 2017/001: SR032; 1 audio cassette
    - Nancy Sweezy reading text of Raised in Clay, undated, AFC 2017/001: SR126; 1 audio cassette
    - Mitchell Shelton on frit machine; Seagrove, North Carolina, undated, AFC 2017/001: SR127; 1 audio cassette
    - Walter Aumen, undated, AFC 2017/001: SR128; 1 audio cassette
- Series 4: National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Site Visits and Apprenticeships, 1977-2004, Bulk: 1984-1994
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - National Apprenticeship Program papers, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 56/7)
    - Apprenticeship conference at SUNY Purchase papers, 1978 (Box-folder 56/8)
    - National Council for Apprenticeship in Art and Craft papers, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 56/9)
    - National Endowment for the Arts papers, 1980-2002 (Box-folder 56/10)
    - Pilot apprenticeship program by the NEA Folk Arts Program notes, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 56/11)
    - Pilot apprenticeship program by the NEA Folk Arts Program notes, 1984 (Box-folder 57/1)
    - Site visit: The Artists Foundation (Boston, Massachusetts), 1982 (Box-folder 57/2)
    - Site visit: Rhode Island State Council on the Arts (Providence, Rhode Island), 1984 (Box-folder 57/3)
    - Site visit: Rhode Island State Council on the Arts (Providence, Rhode Island), 1985 (Box-folder 57/4)
    - Writings - National Endowment for the Arts site visits, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 57/5)
    - Site visit: FieldHi Folk Arts Fair (Vassalboro-Augusta, Maine), 1986 (Box-folder 57/6)
    - Site visit: Refugee Apprenticeship Program (Portland, Oregon), 1987 (Box-folder 57/7)
    - Site visit: Groton Center for the Arts (Groton, Massachusetts), 1989 (Box-folder 57/8)
    - Site visit: Henry Street Settlement (New York, New York), 1989 (Box-folder 57/9)
    - Site visit: Museum of Arts and Sciences / Georgia Clay (Macon, Georgia), 1989 (Box-folder 57/10)
    - Site visit: Jacob's Pillow Dance Festival (Lee, Massachusetts), 1989 (Box-folder 57/11)
    - Site visit: McKissick Museum (Columbia, South Carolina), 1989 (Box-folder 57/12)
    - Site visit: Amana Arts Guild Center (High Amana, Iowa), 1990 (Box-folder 57/13)
    - Site visit: Festival at the Lake / "Local Cultures" (Oakland, California), 1991 (Box-folder 57/14)
    - Site visit: Maine Arts Commission (Augusta, Maine), 1991 (Box-folder 57/15)
    - Site visit: Pennsylvania Heritage Affairs Commission (Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania), 1991 (Box-folder 57/16)
    - Site visit: Ox Millworks (Eureka, California), 1993 (Box-folder 57/17)
    - Site visit: International Jubilee (Knoxville, Tennessee), 1993 (Box-folder 57/18)
    - Site visit: Czech puppetry performance, "Johannes Dokchtor Faust" (New York, New York), 1994 (Box-folder 57/19)
    - Site visit: North Carolina Museum of History (Raleigh, North Carolina), 1994 (Box-folder 57/20)
    - Site visit: Related Material, undated (Box-folder 57/21)
    - National Endowment for the Arts site visits, undated, afc2017001_cf04; text files; original media: CD-ROM
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Quarry site visit for NCTA, 1987, ph09_158 to ph09_168 (Box 21-22)
    - National Endowment for the Arts site visit / Fieldhi Fair, 1986, ph09_199 to ph09_214 (Box 22)
  - Subseries 3: Audio and Video
    - Traditional Arts Apprenticeship, undated, AFC 2017/001: MV08; 1 videotape
- Series 5: Refugee Arts Group (RAG) and the Center for Living Traditions, 1985-1997, Bulk: 1986-1991
  - Subseries 1: Manuscripts and Photographic Prints
    - Refugee Arts Group papers, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 57/22-25)
    - Refugee Arts Group papers, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 58/1-8)
    - Refugee Arts Group papers, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 59/1-2)
    - Refugee Arts Group - "Bamboo" newsletter, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 59/3-5)
    - Refugee Arts Group survey and National Endowment for the Arts grant material, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 59/6)
    - RAG - Lowell Folklife Project, 1987 (Box-folder 59/7)
    - RAG - National Folk Festival, Lowell, Massachusetts, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 59/8)
    - RAG - Lowell Folklife Project interviews, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 59/9)
    - RAG - Lowell Historic Preservation Commission, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 59/10)
    - Refugee Arts Group: Hmong, Vietnamese, Lao, and Kmhmu, 1981-1989, 281 photographic prints (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Refugee camps trip: Thailand, 1986-1986, 18 photographic prints (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Southeast Asian: various performances, 1988-1991, 214 photographic prints (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Southeast Asian: performances, crafts, and artists, 1988-1991, 208 photographic prints (Box-folder 3/1)
    - Southeast Asian: Cambodian, 1988-1991, 40 photographic prints (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Southeast Asian: Hmong, 1988-1991, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Southeast Asian: Vietnamese, 1988-1991, 19 photographic prints (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Southeast Asian: Laos, 1988-1991, 4 photographic prints (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Country Roads: Jugtown, Refugee Arts Group, Center for Living Traditions, Armenia, and portraits, undated, 70 photographic prints (Box-folder 8/2)
    - China, 1986, 4 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/1)
    - Refugee Arts Group: Southeast Asian weaver, undated, 256 photographic prints (Box-folder 10/6)
    - Refugee Arts Group - Lowell, Massachusetts enlarged photographs, ca.1987-1990, 13 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 90/2)
    - Refugee Arts Group: Interview transcripts, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 60/1)
    - "Working with Southeast Asians in Massachusetts" by Nancy Sweezy 1988 Am Folklore Society Centennial Event, 1988 (Box-folder 60/2)
    - Refugee Arts Group - SEA participation in the Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1988 (Box-folder 60/3)
    - Peabody Museum notebook - Keeping Traditions Alive: The Arts of Southeast Asia, 1989 (Box-folder 60/4)
    - Refugee Arts Group - Peabody Museum exhibit, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 60/5)
    - Peabody Museum exhibit text panels - Keeping Traditions Alive: The Arts of Southeast Asia, 1990 (Box-folder 60/6)
    - Peabody Museum exhibit printed material - Keeping Traditions Alive: The Arts of Southeast Asia, 1990 (Box-folder 60/7)
    - Refugee Arts Group - informational photo books, undated, 24 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 60/8)
    - Refugee Arts Group promotional booklet, undated (Box-folder 60/9)
    - Refugee Arts Group - resource material packets for the Southeast Asian Folk Arts Festival, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 60/10)
    - Refugee Arts Group schools program, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 61/1)
    - Country Roads Education Project report by Kathy Neustadt, 1992 (Box-folder 61/2)
    - Refugee Arts Group - Southeast Asian cultural kit for schools, undated (Box-folder 61/3)
    - Teacher's manual for kit on Cambodian culture, undated (Box-folder 61/4)
    - Teacher's manual for kit on Hmong culture, undated (Box-folder 61/5)
    - Refugee Arts Group - Hmong resources, undated (Box-folder 61/6)
    - Refugee Arts Group teacher's manual for kit on Vietnamese culture, undated (Box-folder 61/7)
    - Refugee Arts Group history, 1985-1993, undated (Box-folder 61/8)
    - Refugee Arts Group program announcements, undated (Box-folder 61/9)
    - Refugee Arts Group people resumes, undated (Box-folder 61/10)
    - Refugee Arts Group contact cards, undated (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Southeast Asian artist directory, undated (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Southeast Asian arts information, undated, 1 photographic print and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Southeast Asian arts, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 62/4-6)
    - Clippings regarding Refugee Arts Group people, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Refugee Arts Group Jacob's Pillow, 1991 (Box-folder 62/8)
    - Refugee Arts Group - First Night, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Correspondence and photos - Sarah Magruder, 1997 (Box-folder 62/10)
    - Refugee Arts Group - misc unidentified photos, undated, 10 photographic prints and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Weavers information, 1994, 1 photographic print and mixed manuscript material (Box-folder 62/12)
    - Center for Living Traditions, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 62/13)
    - Center for Living Traditions, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 63/1)
    - Center for Living Traditions newsletter, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 63/2)
    - Center for Living Traditions exhibit panel, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 63/3)
    - Center for Living Traditions, undated, 22 photographic prints (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Center for Living Traditions: exhibit, undated, 97 photographic prints (Box-folder 9/2)
    - Patterned fabric enlargement, undated, AFC 2017/001: OS1-GR01-GR08; 8 black-and-white photographic prints, 16 x 20 in.
    - Refugee Arts Group book layout - transparency, undated, AFC 2017/001: OS1-GR09-GR10; 2 black-and-white transparencies, 19 x 14 in.
    - Patterned fabric enlargement - transparency, undated, AFC 2017/001: OS1-GR11-GR13; 2 black-and-white transparencies, 20 x 16 in.
    - Ukrainian exhibit: Roberson - Binghamton, New York, 1992, 14 photographic prints (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Refugee Arts Group contact sheets, undated, 21 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/9)
    - Center for Living Traditions contact sheets, undated, 2 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/10)
    - Southeast Asian contact sheet: Laos, undated, 6 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/11)
    - Southeast Asian contact sheet: Cambodian, 1988-1999, 8 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/12)
    - Kmhmu contact sheets, undated, 3 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/13)
    - Lowell Festival contact sheets, undated, 8 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/14)
    - Thailand and China contact sheets, undated, 8 photographic prints (Box-folder 87/16)
  - Subseries 2: Slides and Negatives
    - Refugee Arts Group, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph09_001 to ph09_003 (Box 21)
    - BandR Fest/Lowell Festival/SI Festival, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph09_169 to ph09_181 (Box 22)
    - SI Folklife Festival - Japan program potter, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph09_182 to ph09_198 (Box 22)
    - Street and factory pottery, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_001 to ph10_010 (Box 22-24)
    - Commune and folk art - Shanghai, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_011 to ph10_021 (Box 22-24)
    - People's Park/Shanghai Museum, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_022 to ph10_038 (Box 22-24)
    - Tang tomb site, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_039 to ph10_049 (Box 22-24)
    - Suzhou, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_050 to ph10_068 (Box 22-24)
    - Pot distribution center on Yangtze, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_069 to ph10_081 (Box 22-24)
    - Yangtze/ 3 Gorges, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_082 to ph10_101 (Box 22-24)
    - Beijing, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_102 to ph10_113 (Box 22-24)
    - Unlabeled, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_114 to ph10_169 (Box 22-24)
    - Xian/Chengdu, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_170 to ph10_227 (Box 22-24)
    - Chongqing, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_228 to ph10_238 (Box 22-24)
    - Yangtze River trip, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_239 to ph10_258 (Box 22-24)
    - 3 Gorges, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_259 to ph10_287 (Box 22-24)
    - Various scenes, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_288 to ph10_306 (Box 22-24)
    - Suzhou, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_307 to ph10_318 (Box 22-24)
    - Yangtze River, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_319 to ph10_331 (Box 22-24)
    - 1st pottery shop, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_332 to ph10_343 (Box 22-24)
    - 2nd pottery shop, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_344 to ph10_361 (Box 22-24)
    - Factory for tourist go here, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_362 to ph10_374 (Box 22-24)
    - Shanghai and other, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph10_375 to ph10_389 (Box 22-24)
    - Thailand refugee camps - Bangkok, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph11_001 to ph11_066 (Box 24-25)
    - KID refugee camp, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph11_067 to ph11_166 (Box 24-25)
    - Thailand refugee camps, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph11_167 to ph11_349 (Box 24-25)
    - Cambodian/TCM Festival, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph12_001 to ph12_018 (Box 25-27)
    - Cambodian/National Folk Festival, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph12_019 to ph12_052 (Box 25-27)
    - Chea Uy and Group/MFA Performance, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph12_053 to ph12_068 (Box 25-27)
    - Saroeun Hing, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph12_069 to ph12_083 (Box 25-27)
    - New Year Brighton/Lowell Festival, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph12_084 to ph12_102 (Box 25-27)
    - Laotian Handwork project, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph12_103 to ph12_120 (Box 25-27)
    - Laotian celebration/Brighton, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph12_121 to ph12_135 (Box 25-27)
    - Laotian participants/Smithsonian Folklife Festival, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_136 to ph12_152 (Box 25-27)
    - Laotian dance, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_153 to ph12_176 (Box 25-27)
    - Laotian cafts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_177 to ph12_194 (Box 25-27)
    - Unlabeled, Laotian, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph12_195 to ph12_228 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong performances, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_229 to ph12_277 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong at Folklife Festival, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph12_278 to ph12_296 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong Paj Taub, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_297 to ph12_315 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong traditional clothing, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_316 to ph12_335 (Box 25-27)
    - Ying Yang Lee - Springfield, Massachusetts, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_336 to ph12_355 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong story textiles, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_356 to ph12_375 (Box 25-27)
    - Hmong textiles, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph12_376 to ph12_395 (Box 25-27)
    - Kmhmu sword dance, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph13_001 to ph13_027 (Box 27-29)
    - Kmhmu instruments and artifacts, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph13_028 to ph13_047 (Box 27-29)
    - Talay Sivilay / Kmhmu apprenticeship, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph13_048 to ph13_057 (Box 27-29)
    - Vietnamese saw art, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph13_058 to ph13_067 (Box 27-29)
    - Thong Phamduy/Vietnamese apprenticeship, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph13_068 to ph13_098 (Box 27-29)
    - Lowell Festival, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph13_099 to ph13_158 (Box 27-29)
    - Kim Chi Porter and family, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph13_159 to ph13_167 (Box 27-29)
    - Nguyen Dinh Nghia and family, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph13_168 to ph13_215 (Box 27-29)
    - Unlabeled, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph13_216 to ph13_319 (Box 27-29)
    - Lowell Festival, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph21_001 to ph21_015 (Box 43)
    - KID, Site 2, and B.V. - Thailand, 1986-1998, AFC 2017/001: ph21_016 to ph21_029 (Box 43)
    - Lowell Angkor Dance Troupe, 1990, AFC 2017/001: ph21_030 to ph21_059 (Box 43)
    - Refugee Arts Group Book, undated, AFC 2017/001: ph24_001; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Cambodian Wedding, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_003 to ph24_005; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Allston / Brighton Ethnic Festival, 1986, AFC 2017/001: ph24_006 to ph24_007; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - National Folk Festival, 1987, AFC 2017/001: ph24_008; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Smithsonian Festival of American Folklife, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph24_009 to ph24_010; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Festival of Maine Folklife, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph24_011; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Talay Sivilai apprenticeship, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph24_012 to ph24_013; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Apprenticeship, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_014; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Festival Survey, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_015; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Hmong Exhibit at Peabody Museum, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_016 to ph24_017; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Peabody Museum Survey, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_018; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Lao/Hmong Peabody exhibit, 1989, AFC 2017/001: ph24_019 to ph24_020; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)
    - Hmong New Year, 1988, AFC 2017/001: ph24_021; film negatives, color; 35 mm. (Box 45)